rage3d.com 2002-10-04

# Rage3D : Privacy Statement

Rage3d.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of you as a user of this Website. This Website does not collect Personal Information about you except for information that you voluntarily provide (for example, when you submit an email to us with comments about our web site or products reviewed on the web site and you do not specifically indicate that the information contained within is to be considered confidential or provide answers to a voluntary readership survey.) 

We consider the following to be Personal Information: your name, address, phone number, date of birth, job, personal interests, credit card information, your e-mail address and data about the pages you visited on this Website... 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to deliver preferred content and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our forum. 

This site contains links to other sites. Rage3d.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, and forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

Please email: [news@rage3d.com](mailto:news@rage3d.com)

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact. 

_Rage3D_ _[mrb@rage3d.com](mailto:mrb@rage3d.com)_
